Guide to the Gay male pornographic movies, circa 1970-1990
Gay male pornographic movies,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay male pornographic movies, circa 1970-1990
7637
7 cubic feet.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay male pornographic 8mm films; packages depict and characterize the sale of such material.
Also, VHS tapes and DVDs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Gay male pornographic 8mm films; packages depict and characterize the sale of such material.
Also, VHS tapes and DVDs.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Pornography.; Sex in mass media.; Pornography; Sex in mass media
Form and Genre Terms:
Motion pictures.; Erotica.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Archival copies not to be played.
NOTES
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Reel to Reel Films
Series II. Videos
Series III. DVDs
CONTAINER LIST
- Reel to Reel Films
  - Call Boys #2: Making a Mistake, Undated; TR-11558 (Box 1)
  - Call Boys #3: Callboys At Home, Undated; TR-11559 (Box 1)
  - Erotic Hands Part 2, Undated; TR-11560-11563 (Box 1)
    Duplicate included
  - The Gay Blades #9: "Rick Cassidy: Playmate of the Year: Part I, Undated; TR-16035 (Box 1)
  - Horse No. 807: "Shove More Up My Ass", Undated; TR-11564 (Box 1)
  - Horse No. 810: "Caught In the Air", Undated; TR-11565 (Box 1)
  - Horse No. 811: "Fuck Muscle", Undated; TR-11566 (Box 1)
  - How the West Was One # 4: The Law Comes, Undated; TR-11567 (Box 1)
  - How the West Was One #3: Ranch Fever, Undated; TR-11568 (Box 1)
  - Knights of the Night #1: The Crisco Kids, Undated; TR-11569 (Box 1)
  - Knights of the Night #3: The Sling, Undated; TR-11570 (Box 1)
  - Knights of the Night #4: Defiled Fascist, Undated; TR-11571 (Box 1)
  - Knights of the Night #6: A Hard Lesson, Undated; TR-11572 (Box 1)
  - Sextravagent #1: Suck, Undated; TR-16028 (Box 1)
  - Colt Studio Film, 1979; TR-16036, TR-16037; Cult Studio (Box 2)
  - Brentwood Collectors' Edition #273: Bruno & Shane, 1983; TR-16038; Brentwood Studios (Box 2)
  - Dante's Inferno #1: The Hitch Hiker, Undated; TR-16039 (Box 2)
  - Dante's Inferno #3: The Hawker, Undated; TR-16040 (Box 2)
  - The Gay Blades #4: "Magazine Love", Undated; TR-16045 (Box 2)
  - The Gay Blades #10: "Rick Cassidy: Playmate of the Year" Part II, Undated; TR-16046 (Box 2)
  - Hot Rods #3: Fuck Truck, Undated; TR-16047 (Box 2)
  - Magnum Griffin Collection: Cell Block - Part 2, Undated; TR-16048 (Box 2)
  - Magnum Griffin Collection: Pumping Nine, Undated; TR-16049 (Box 2)
  - Muscle #4: "Smell of Leather", Undated; TR-16050 (Box 2)
  - Rough Riders #4: Dreams, Undated; TR-16051 (Box 2)
  - Super Gay #1, Undated; TR-16052 (Box 2)
  - Stallions #905: Brandon & Steve, Undated; TR-16053 (Box 2)
  - Truck Stop, Undated; TR-16054 (Box 2)
  - The NM Series, 1972; TR-16055 (Box 3)
  - Playmates #11: Wild Beauty, 1973; TR-16056; Playmate Films (Box 3)
  - Brentwood #701: Blue Streak, Undated; TR-16057 (Box 3)
  - Brentwood Collectors' Edition #150: The Lifeguard, Undated; TR-16058 (Box 3)
  - Call Boys #2: Making a Mistake, Undated; TR-16059 (Box 3)
  - Centurions, Undated; TR-16060 (Box 3)
  - Chaps #5001: Wild in the Woods, Undated; TR-16061 (Box 3)
  - Chaps #5002: The Expert, Undated; TR-16062 (Box 3)
  - Chaps #5004: Open Season Part. 2, Undated; TR-16063 (Box 3)
  - Chaps #5006: We Deliver, Undated; TR-16064 (Box 3)
  - Deep Treat, Undated; TR-16065 (Box 3)
  - Dream Boy Films #5: Dreary Brothers, Undated; TR-16066 (Box 3)
  - Gay Knight Classic #101, Undated; TR-16067 (Box 3)
  - Gay Knight Classic #103, Undated; TR-16068 (Box 3)
  - Gay Knight Classic #104, Undated; TR-16069 (Box 3)
  - Horse #805: "shove that dick down his straight throat", Undated; TR-16070 (Box 3)
  - Horse #806: "cum'n' get it", Undated; TR-16071 (Box 3)
  - Impulse Impulse Impulse #3: Sun, Undated; TR-16072-16073 (Box 3)
  - Impulse Impulse Impulse #4: Dinner, Undated; TR-16074 (Box 3)
  - Impulse Impulse Impulse #5: Workout, Undated; TR-16075 (Box 3)
  - Interludes #6: "Steve and Tony", Undated; TR-16076 (Box 3)
  - Love In Scandinavia: Teen Agers, Undated; TR-16077; Lasse Braun Productions (Box 3)
  - Magnum Griffin Collection: Jim & John, Undated; TR-16078 (Box 3)
  - Magnum Griffin Collection: Michael & Phillip - Part 1, Undated; TR-16079 (Box 3)
  - Playmates #19: Private Party, Undated; TR-16080
  - Ram Rods #307: Jeff Noll Adventure Part 1, Undated; TR-16081 (Box 3)
  - Scandia, Undated; TR-16082-16083 (Box 3)
  - Sextool Part 1: The Sailor, Undated; TR-16084; Cosco (Box 3)
  - Sextool Part 4: The Boxer, Undated; TR-16085; Cosco (Box 3)
  - Show Hards #3: I Found It At the Movies, Undated; TR-16086 (Box 3)
  - Working Men #6: The Mechanics, Undated; TR-16087 (Box 3)
- Videos
  - Song of the Loom, 1985; V-10294; Herbert, Andrew; Sawyer Productions, Ltd. (Box 4)
  - Black Attack, 1987; V-10295; Catalina Video (Box 4)
  - Sex Oasis, 1989; Cadinot, Jean-Daniel; Paladin Productions (Box 4)
  - Asian Force, 1991; V-10298; Chan, Tony; Asian Man Video; Associated Video Group Inc (Box 4)
  - Black Salsa, 1991; V-10299; Filmco Video (Box 4)
  - Every Night in Thailand, 1991; V-10296; A Lotus Blossom Production (Box 4)
  - Fantasy in Chiang Mai, 1991; V-10297; A Lotus Blossom Production (Box 4)
  - Pattaya Pleasures, 1991; V-10313; A Lotus Blossom Production (Box 4)
  - Black and Ready, 1992; V-10303; Filmco Video (Box 4)
  - Black Trade, 1992; V-10300; A Studio XYZ Production; Black Nights Video (Box 4)
  - Ghetto Guys, 1992; V-10301; Filmco Video (Box 4)
  - Black Passion, 1993; V-10306; Black Star Productions (Box 4)
  - Steam Heat, 1993; V-10305; Black Knights Video (Box 4)
  - Wet Thai Stories Series 3 Deja-Vu, 1995; Oggi; Exotic Productions (Box 4)
  - Beyond Paradise, 1996; V-10308; Hayman, John; Video 10 Distributors (Box 4)
  - Black Jacks No. Two, 1996; V-10307; Leisure Time Entertainment (Box 4)
  - Rice Prince Vol. 2, 1996; Birlynn Productions Asia (Box 4)
  - Asian Dreams Vol. 3, 1997; V-10310; Birlynn Productions Asia (Box 4)
  - Asian Studs Vol. 3, 1997; V-10309; Birlynn Productions Asia (Box 4)
  - Erogenous Zone, 1998; Oggi; Exotic Productions (Box 4)
  - Geisha Boys Volume #2, 1998; V-10311; Typhoon Pictures, Inc. (Box 4)
  - Black From Behind, 2000; Video 10 Distributors (Box 4)
  - Chocolate Dessert, 1996-12; V-10312; Ford, Rick (Box 4)
  - Asian Bodybuilders in Hot Core No. 2, Undated; V-10315; B.A. & Asian Productions (Box 4)
  - Black African Gold (Hardcore), Undated; The French Connection (Box 4)
  - Black Hombres 1 Black Western Ranch Sex, Undated; V-10314; Ross, Frank; Satellite Video (Box 4)
  - The Worst Boy in Town, Vadillo, Enrique Gomez; 99 (Box 4)
  - Black Workout, 1984; V-10377; Arden, Scott; Sterling, Loren; Thunderbolt (Box 5)
  - The Best of Black Knights Video, 1991; V-10317; Black Knights Video (Box 5)
  - Blacks Working Hard, 1991; V-10318; Pleasure Productions (Box 5)
  - The Nasty Groove, 1992; V-10319; Top Man Video (Box 5)
  - Thai Erotica, 1992; V-10320; Oggi; Exotic Productions (Box 5)
  - Hot Shades, 1993; V-10322; Black Star (Box 5)
  - How Ya Like Me Now?, 1993; V-10323; Black Knights Video (Box 5)
  - Black Street Fever, 1995; Paris, T.J.; All Worlds Video (Box 5)
  - Asian Giants Vol. 1, 1996; V-10324; Birlynn Productions / Asia (Box 5)
  - Rice Prince Vol. 1, 1996; V-10325; Birlynn Productions / Asia (Box 5)
  - Oriental Islanders, 1997; V-10326; Bakal, Marco; Bacchus (Box 5)
  - Geisha Boys Volume #1, 1998; V-10327; Typhoon Pictures, Inc. (Box 5)
  - Joy Toy, 2000; V-10328; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 5)
  - Act of Passion, 1999-2001; Oggi; Exotic Productions (Box 5)
  - Boys of Bangkok, Undated; V-10329; Mahler, Wolfgang; Geschaft Productions (Box 5)
  - Lady Boys, Undated; V-10330 (Box 5)
  - Made in the Shade Part II, Undated; Ross, Frank; Satellite Video (Box 5)
  - School Ties In Asian, Undated; B.A. & Asian Production (Box 5)
  - Sex Messengers, 1987; V-10333; Satellite Video (Box 6)
  - Deeper & Deeper, 1993; V-10335; Black Knights Video (Box 6)
  - For a Lost Soldier, 1994; V-10337; Kerbosch, Roeland; Award Films International (Box 6)
  - Ricky's Revenge, 2001; V-10338; Black Box Productions (Box 6)
  - Capoeira #9, 2003; V-10339 (Box 6)
  - Capoeira #10, 2003; V-10340 (Box 6)
  - Charlie's Asians, 2003-04-03; V-10341; Jackson, Richard; asianguys.com videos (Box 6)
  - Mandingo Men #3, 2004; V-10343; Bacchus (Box 6)
  - Thai Boxer In Fighting & In Loving, Undated; V-10344; B.A. & Asian (Box 6)
  - Black Brothers, 1984; V-10345, V-10346; Checker Board Video (Box 7)
    Contains duplicate
  - Black Sex Party, 1988; V-10354; Haggerty, Mike; Filmco Video (Box 7)
  - Geisha Boys Volume 2, 1998; V-10347; Typhoon Pictures Inc. (Box 7)
  - The Best of Black Knights Video, 1991; V-10348; Black Knights Video (Box 7)
  - Blacks Working Hard, 1991; V-10349; Pleasure Productions (Box 7)
  - Ghetto Guys Volume 2, 1993; Filmco Video (Box 7)
  - Ghetto Guys Volume 3, 1993; V-10350; Filmco Video (Box 7)
  - Three Ways, 1993; V-10351; HIS Video (Box 7)
  - Afro SleazyAct, 1994; V-10352; Black Star Productions (Box 7)
  - Hot Rodd, 1994; V-10353; HIS Video (Box 7)
  - Wet Thai Stories Volume 1 Room Service, 1994; V-10355; Oggi; Exotic Productions (Box 7)
  - Dj Vu, 1995; V-10356; Oggi; Exotic Productions (Box 7)
  - Asian Dreams #3, 1997; V-10357; Bacchus (Box 7)
  - Black & Huge Size Does Matter #2, 1998; Rebel Video (Box 7)
  - Handful of Joy, 1998; V-10359, V-10360; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 7)
  - Asian Giants #2, 1999; V-10362; Filmco Video (Box 7)
  - Rice Prince #2, 1999; V-10363; Filmco Video (Box 7)
  - Dream Chasers, 2000; V-10364; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 7)
  - Act of Passion, 2001; V-10365; Oggi (Box 7)
  - Erogenous Zone, 2001; V-10366; Oggi; Exotic Productions (Box 7)
  - Primal Passion, 2001; V-10367; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 7)
  - Stirring Yearnings, 2001; V-10368; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 7)
  - Asian Bodybuilders in Hot Core No. 1, Undated; V-10369; B.A. & Asian (Box 7)
  - Blackmale, Undated; V-10371; Infinity Video (Box 7)
  - Lady Boys #2, Undated; V-10373 (Box 7)
  - Jerry McGuire, Undated; V-10374 (Box 7)
  - Made in the Shade Part I, Undated; V-10375 (Box 7)
  - Recruit Me!, Undated; V-10376; BFP Video (Box 7)
  - Black Delivery, 1986; V-10379; Ross, Frank; Sattelite Video (Box 8)
  - Humungous, 1986; Sattelite Video (Box 8)
  - Black All-American, 1990; V-10381 (Box 8)
  - Afternoon Fun, 1991; Lotus Blossom Productions (Box 8)
  - Absolutely Sex, 1993; V-10382 (Box 8)
  - Tenderly Thai, 1994; V-10383; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 8)
  - Black Street Fever, 1995; V-10399 (Box 8)
  - Butt-Stuffing Bears, 1995; V-10384; HIS Video (Box 8)
  - Cops, Jocks, and Military Feet, 1995; V-10385; HIS Video (Box 8)
  - Soulful Food, 1998; Ford, Christopher; All Worlds Video (Box 8)
  - Touched By The Stars, 1998; V-10387; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 8)
  - Edge of Enchantment, 1999; V-10388; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 8)
  - Looks To Sigh For, 1999; V-10389; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 8)
  - More Joy, 1999; V-10396, V-10397; Island Caprice Studios (Box 8)
  - Black African Gold - Hardcore, 2001; V-10391; Cream of the Crop Production (Box 8)
  - The Desire Game, 2001; V-10392; Hayman, John; Island Caprice Studios (Box 8)
  - Platino Boys, Undated; V-10395 (Box 8)
    Title unclear
  - Previews Vol. 1, Undated; V-10398; Award Films (Box 8)
  - Unmarked VHS tape, Undated; V-10316 (Box 8)
  - Black Orient Express, 1985; V-10378; Checker Board Video (Box 9)
  - Men of Vivid 4, 1989; V-10380; Vivid Man (Box 9)
  - Sex Oasis, 1990; V-10400; Bjorn, Kristen (Box 9)
  - Black Workout Part 3, 1991; V-10334; Filmco Video (Box 9)
  - Throbbing Black, 1992; V-10302; Top Man Video (Box 9)
  - Deeper & Deeper, 1993; V-10321; Black Knights Video (Box 9)
  - Ghetto Guys #2, 1993; V-10336; Filmco Video (Box 9)
    Can be found in "Getto Guys Volume 3" container
  - Sweaty Menz in the Shower, 1993; V-10304; Black Knights Video (Box 9)
  - Healing, 1995; V-10386; Oggi; Exotic Producitons (Box 9)
  - Black + Huge, 1997; V-10358; Rebel Video (Box 9)
  - Soulful Food, 1998; V-10361; All Worlds Video (Box 9)
  - Black Hole, 2000; V-10446; King, Alex; Ebony Vid International (Box 9)
  - Black Samuel, 2000; V-10390; King, Alex; Ebony Vid International (Box 9)
  - La Grande Sduction, 2004; V-10342; Pouliot, Jean-Franois; Max Films (Box 9)
  - Black & Huge No. 3, Undated; V-10393 (Box 9)
  - Blacklode, Undated; V-10370; Marksman Productions (Box 9)
  - The Gay Team, Undated; V-10332; Win-Chester Productions (Box 9)
    Can be found in "Black Brothers" container
  - Humungus, Undated; V-10372 (Box 9)
  - Made in the Shade Part II, Undated; V-10394 (Box 9)
  - Platino Boys Thai Boat-Trip, Undated; V-10331; GERO; VKR Pictures (Box 9)
  - Unmarked VHS Tapes, Undated; V-10441, V-10443, V-10445 (Box 9)
- DVDs
  - Blissfully Yours, 2004; DVD-2388; Weerasethakul,Apichatpong; Anna Sanders Film (Box 5)
  - Mysterious Object at Noon, 2004; DVD-2389; Weerasethakul,Apichatpong; Anna Sanders Film (Box 5)
  - Macho Dancer, 2005; DVD-2390-2391; Brocka, Lino; Viva Platinum (Box 5)
  - My Last Round, 2011; DVD-2392; Jorquera, Julio; tla releasing (Box 5)
  - Undertow, 2011; DVD-2393; Fuentes-Len, Javier; Wolfe (Box 5)
  - Eroddity(s), 2014; DVD-2394; Vasquez, Steve; tla releasing (Box 5)
  - Floating Skyscrapers, 2014; DVD-2395; Wasilewski, Tomasz; tla releasing, Canteen Outlaws (Box 5)
  - The Last Match, 2014; DVD-2396; Hens, Antonio; Canteen Outlaws (Box 5)
  - Man at Bath, 2014; DVD-2397; Honroe, Christopher; Canteeen Outlaws (Box 5)
  - A Fighter's Blues, 2000; DVD-2398; Lee, Daniel; Teamwork Motion Pictures (Box 6)
  - Capoeira 5, 2003; DVD-2399 (Box 6)
  - Gone, But Not Forgotten, 2003; DVD-2400; Akers, Michael D.; United Gaynetwork (Box 6)
  - Lockdown, 2003; Luessenhop, John; Pal Pictures (Box 6)
  - Cherry Boy Asia, 2004; DVD-2401 (Box 6)
  - Dream Boys #2, 2004; DVD-2402; Bacchus, Birlynn Production (Box 6)
  - the hole, 2004; DVD-2403; West, Wash; tla releasing, Jet Set Productions (Box 6)
    DVD container still encased in plastic wrapping
  - Locked Up, 2004; DVD-2404; Amndreas, Joerg; tla releasing, Cazzo Films (Box 6)
  - Mandingo Men 3, 2004; DVD-2405; Bacchus (Box 6)
  - Brother to Brother, 2005; DVD-2406; Wolfe (Box 6)
  - Bustin' Out, 2005; DVD-2407; Decklin; Jackrabbit Releasing (Box 6)
  - Exposed The Making of a Legend, 2005; DVD-2408; Mr. Pam; Colt Studio Group (Box 6)
  - Mandingo Men 5, 2005; DVD-2409; Bacchus (Box 6)
  - Parallel Sons, 2005; DVD-2410; Young, John G.; Strand Releasing (Box 6)
  - The Reception, 2005; DVD-2411; Young, John G.; Strand Releasing (Box 6)
  - Boys Love, 2006; DVD-2412; Terauchi, Kohtaro; Picture This! Entertainment (Box 6)
  - Jokion Boy, 2006; DVD-2413; GayAsianAmateurs.com (Box 6)
  - Clandestinos, 2007; DVD-2414; Hens, Antonio; tla releasing, Malas Companias (Box 6)
  - Rock Haven, 2007; DVD-2415; Lewis, David; tla releasing, Morning View Films (Box 6)
  - Just Say Love, 2008; Humphreys, Bill; Here! Films (Box 6)
  - Kambyo, 2008; DVD-2416; Altarejos, Joselito; Viva Video, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Running Deep, 2008; DVD-2417; Kokkoros, Mark; Arztical Entertainment (Box 6)
  - Asian Queer Shorts, 2009; DVD-2418; frameline (Box 6)
  - Children of God, 2009; DVD-2419; Mortimer, Kareem; tla releasing, Mercury Rising Media (Box 6)
  - Finding Me, 2009; DVD-2420; Omeus Jr., Roger S.; tla releasing, OmeProductions, LLC. (Box 6)
  - From Beginning to End, 2009; DVD-2421; Abranches, Aluzio; tla releasing (Box 6)
  - Little Boy Big Boy, 2009; DVD-2422; Altarejos, Joselito; Viva Video, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Raging Sun, Raging Sky, 2009; DVD-2423; Hernandez, Julio; tla releasing (Box 6)
  - Spring Fever, 2009; DVD-2424; Ye, Lou; Dream Factory, Rosem Films (Box 6)
  - Mixed Kebab, 2012; DVD-2425; Thys, Guy Lee; tla releasing (Box 6)
  - Untitled Electric Eel Film, 2012; DVD-2426; Electric Eel Films (Box 6)
  - Ben & Sam, Undated; DVD-2440; Bacolod, Mark Shandii; Imaginative Media Production, OXIN Entertainment (Box 6)
  - Daybreak, Undated; DVD-2427; Alix Jr., Adolfo Borinaga; Videoflick Productions. Inc. (Box 6)
  - Duda Doubt, Undated; DVD-2428-2429; Viva Video, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Rendezvous at the Golden Gate Bed & Breakfast, 1998; DVD-2430, DVD-2433; Greenwood Cooper Homevideo (Box 7)
    Also contains disc for Just Say Love (DVD-2433)
  - The Map of Sex and Love, 2003; DVD-2431; Chan, Evans; Water Bearer Films (Box 7)
  - Strange Fruit, 2005; DVD-2432, DVD-2434; Kyle Shickner (Box 7)
    Also contains disc for Lockdown (DVD-2434)
  - Samurai Boys Stand By Me!, Date Unknown; DVD-2435; Matsuoka, Tsubasa; Studio Happy Chicken (Box 7)
  - F/Stop, 2005; DVD-2436; ARI Productions (Box 8)
  - Bathhouse, 2007; DVD-2437; Pablo, Crisaldo; Water Bearer Films (Box 8)
  - Friends Forever, 2007; DVD-2438; Henszelman, Stephen; Water Bearer Films (Box 8)
  - Speechless, 2012; DVD-2439; Chung, Simon; QC Cinema (Box 8)